import mysql.connector as sc
c = sc.connect(host="localhost", user="root", password="Ritesh")
cursor = c.cursor()

d = {0: {'question': 'Apprentice and successor of Elijah is wildly regarded as?', 'option_a': 'A. Elisha', 'option_b': 'Elsa', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 1: {'question': 'Who is the founder of the Slug Club?', 'option_a': 'A. Horace Slughorn', 'option_b': 'Incendon Slug', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 2: {'question': 'What us the tallest animal of the world?', 'option_a': 'A.Giraffe', 'option_b': 'Shark', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 3: {'question': 'How much money does the average player spend on Fortnite?', 'option_a': '$60', 'option_b': '$200', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 4: {'question': 'Which is the only U.S. state capital city with not a single McDonald fast food joint?', 'option_a': 'Montpelier, Vermont', 'option_b': 'California', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 5: {'question': 'The shortest verse in the Holy Book is?', 'option_a': 'Jesus wept', 'option_b': 'Henry', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 6: {'question': 'Which mathematician has an Erdos number of zero (0)?', 'option_a': 'Paul Erdos', 'option_b': 'Euler', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 7: {'question': 'What is the average salary of an NFL player?', 'option_a': '$2 Million', 'option_b': '$1 Million', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 8: {'question': 'What country gave the United States its famous Statue of Liberty as a gift in 1886?', 'option_a': 'France', 'option_b': 'Spain', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 9: {'question': 'Who won the wheelchair mens singles of the Australian Open 2011 Championship?', 'option_a': 'Shingo Kunieda', 'option_b': 'Deep Singh', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 10: {'question': 'Snow White was befriended and lived with how many dwarfs?', 'option_a': '7', 'option_b': '11', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 11: {'question': 'Which music legend was murdered on April Day of Fool, 1984?', 'option_a': 'Marvin Gaye', 'option_b': 'Bob Marley', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 12: {'question': 'What is the name of the capital city of France?', 'option_a': 'Paris', 'option_b': 'London', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 13: {'question': 'In 1979, Bob was the first one of these to be given a male name. What is it?', 'option_a': 'The Hurricane', 'option_b': 'The Typhoon', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 14: {'question': 'Where was the first McDonald restaurant located?', 'option_a': 'California', 'option_b': 'Washington DC.', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 15: {'question': 'Which famous American pop singer was actually born in the State of Hawaii?', 'option_a': 'Bruno Mars', 'option_b': 'Post Malone', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 16: {'question': 'What is the first of the four cups of wine diners are obligated to drink at the Passover Seder meant for?', 'option_a': 'Kiddush', 'option_b': 'Feddish', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 17: {'question': 'The word Pok√©mon is generally understood to be a translation of which phrase?', 'option_a': 'Pocket Monster', 'option_b': 'Pocket Man', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 18: {'question': 'What is the name of the Capital Of New Zealand that is the Southernmost Capital in the world? ', 'option_a': 'Wellington', 'option_b': 'New Wellington', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 19: {'question': 'Brazil was once a colony of which European country?', 'option_a': 'Potugal', 'option_b': 'Spain', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 20: {'question': 'What was Mickey Mouse name before it was changed to Mickey?', 'option_a': 'Mortimer', 'option_b': 'Morty', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 21: {'question': 'What is a group of Crows called?', 'option_a': 'Murder', 'option_b': 'Shoal', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 22: {'question': 'In a movie title Elvis Presley said Viva to where?', 'option_a': 'Las Vegas', 'option_b': 'Rio de Janerio', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 23: {'question': 'What Minnesota Congresswoman dropped her U.S. presidential bid after the 2012 Iowa Caucus?', 'option_a': 'Michele Bachmann', 'option_b': 'John F. Kennedy', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 24: {'question': 'What city is the capital of China?\t', 'option_a': 'Beijing', 'option_b': 'Shanghai', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 25: {'question': 'What is the fastest fish in the Ocean?', 'option_a': 'Sailfish', 'option_b': 'Shark', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 26: {'question': 'The Rungnado May Day Stadium, built in honor of the May Day holiday, exists in which country?', 'option_a': 'North Korea', 'option_b': 'South Korea', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 27: {'question': 'How many time zones are there in the world?', 'option_a': '24', 'option_b': '35', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 28: {'question': 'Which is the highest-grossing Harry Potter film?', 'option_a': 'Deathly Hallows 2', 'option_b': 'Goblet Of Fire', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 29: {'question': 'What do you fear if you suffer from claustrophobia?', 'option_a': 'Being in an enclosed space', 'option_b': 'Fear from Darkness', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 30: {'question': 'May Day festivities are traditionally linked to the celebration of what?', 'option_a': 'Fertility', 'option_b': 'Prosperity', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 31: {'question': 'Pete Sampras is a legendary tennis player. Which nation is he from?', 'option_a': 'USA', 'option_b': 'France', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 32: {'question': 'Red and what other color are most associated with Valentine Day?', 'option_a': 'Pink', 'option_b': 'Blue', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 33: {'question': 'In England, there is the modern May Day tradition of jumping off the Magdalen Bridge into the waters below. Where is this bridge located?', 'option_a': 'Oxford', 'option_b': 'Havard', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 34: {'question': 'Which electronic musical instrument emits the eeriest of sounds and is the only instrument played without touching it?', 'option_a': 'Theremin', 'option_b': 'The Glass Harmonica', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 35: {'question': 'Who played Nuke Laloosh in Bull Durham?', 'option_a': 'Tim Robbins', 'option_b': 'Jhonny Depp', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 36: {'question': 'The lowest region of the atmosphere of Earth comes between the earth and the stratosphere, what is this regions name?', 'option_a': 'Troposphere', 'option_b': 'Stratosphere', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 37: {'question': 'The Doak Walker Award is given annually to the top college player at which position?', 'option_a': 'Running Back', 'option_b': 'Running Front', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}, 38: {'question': 'Which beverage is advertised as being Sports Fuel?', 'option_a': 'Gatorade', 'option_b': 'Red Bull', 'option_c': 'I do not know', 'Correct_option': 'a'}}
cursor.execute("create database trivia43;")
cursor.execute("use trivia43;")
cursor.execute("create table questions(question varchar(200),option_a varchar(100),option_b varchar(100), option_c varchar(50) default 'I do not know',correct_option varchar(50),Serial_Number int(10));")

for r in d:
    question = d[r]["question"]
    option_a = d[r]["option_a"]
    option_b = d[r]["option_b"]
    option_c = d[r]["option_c"]
    Correct_option = d[r]['Correct_option']
    Serial_Number = r
    statement = "insert into questions values('{}','{}','{}','{}','{}',{})".format(question, option_a, option_b, option_c, Correct_option, Serial_Number)
    cursor.execute(statement)
c.commit()


